Feena, Tsz Ling, Fung

IT Developer

Toronto, ON, Canada

feenafungftl@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/feena-fung/

Summary

Dedicated developer with more than 2 years of experience in IT industry. Skills include programming, systems analysis and design, cloud computing. Eager to learn and love to take challenges. Seeking to use proven skills in supporting the efficient delivery of quality IT solutions and services.

Skills & Abilities

Language Chinese: Mandarin (Fluent), Cantonese (Native)

English: Fluent

• IELTS 6.5 (Listening 7.0, Reading 6.5, Writing 6.5, Speaking 6.0)

• TOEIC (Listening & Reading 920/990, Speaking & Writing 320/400)

Programming & Databases (Oracle SQL, Progressql), Object-oriented Programming (Java,

Framework Python, SpringBoot), Web Development (JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, React),

VBA

Others Cloud Computing (AWS, Azure), Knowledge of DevOps

Experience

Analyst Programmer | IBM China/Hong Kong Limited, Hong Kong Feb 2021 - Feb 2022

• Develop data warehouse and ETL solutions with AWS and Informatica

Project: revenue management system data (Cathay Pacific Airways Ltd)

Programmer | DXC Technology Limited, Hong Kong May 2020 - Feb 2021

• Responsible for application development with **Java**, Spring, JSP, jQuery, Hibernate and Oracle DB

• Project: construction and building service contractor performance assessment system (Hong Kong Housing Authority)

ICT Graduate Trainee | PCCW Solutions Limited, Hong Kong Aug 2019 - May 2020

- Engaged in enterprise application development (User Interface and API) with React, LESS, Typescript, Java, SpringBoot
- Project: investor and registered financial institution license application review and approval system (Securities and Futures Commission, Hong Kong)

Education

City University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong Bachelor of Business Administration with Second Class Honours, Upper Division Major: Business Analysis (Management Science) Minors: Information Management for Financial Services & Computing

• Courses include **Systems Analysis and Design** (A), Business Programming with Spreadsheet (A), **Big Data Analytics** (A), Business Intelligence and Analytics (A-), **Java Programming** (B+)

Victoria University of Wellington, New Zealand

Jul 2017 - Nov 2017

Student Exchange Program (Faculty of Information Management)

• Courses include **Databases** (A+), Business Analytics (B+)

Qualification

AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate AWS Training and Certification	Jan 2022
Build secure and robust solutions using architectural design principles (scalability,	
resiliency, efficiency, fault-tolerance) based on customer requirements	
Microsoft Certified Azure Data Fundamental Microsoft Corporation	Jul 2021
Microsoft Certified Azure Al Fundamental Microsoft Corporation	Jun 2021
Microsoft Certified Azure Fundamental Microsoft Corporation	May 2021
• Knowledge of cloud concepts, Azure services, security and privacy in Azure	
SAS Certified Predicative Modeler Using SAS Enterprise Miner 14	Jan 2019
SAS Institute Incorporation	
• Prepare data, build predictive models and perform pattern analysis	
SAS Certified Base Programmer for SAS 9 SAS Institute Incorporation	Jun 2017
Activities	

COOLTHINK@Jockey Club Ambassador

Jan 2017 - May 2018

The Hong Kong Jockey Club Charities Trust

Internal Secretary of Social Services Team

May 2016 - Feb 2017

• City University of Hong Kong Students' Union